So many times I thought I would forget myself...
... and open my heart to place at your feet.
Touching your feet...
...I would say...
... how much I love you, my fiancée, secretly.
Touching your feet.... I would say...
I considered...
... you to be a goddess of heaven
How could I utter the words of passion to you!
I decided in my mind ...
... I would stay away
I would ever adore you alone in seclusion
I decided in my mind...
... I would stay away
I would ever adore you alone in seclusion
Nobody will know...
... about my deep passion
Nobody will see...
... the collection of my tears
Today when you come to ask yourself...
... how can I express how much I love you!
So many times I thought I would forget myself...
... and open my heart to place at your feet